DIMITRIS RAMMOS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

jrammos@outlook.com.gr +30 6940870953 Athens, Greece

LinkedIn Profile GitHub My Portfolio

Profile Summary

I am 22 years old and I live in Athens. I am a Junior Software Developer at Entersoft. I am an undergraduate student in Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, University of Athens. I like programming, and web development, in the future I would like to work in fields such as artificial intelligence and cyber security. You can read about me and my projects in <u>My Portfolio</u>.

Skills

- C/C++
- Rust
- Python

- MySQL
- Assembly

- C#
- Java
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Git
- Agile

Education

Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, NKUA

OCT 2019-PRESENT

You can read about the department here

Work Experience

Junior Software Developer - Entersoft

SEP 2023 - PRESENT

- I work as a Mobile developer and I coding C# .Net for cross applications(xamarin.ios, xamarin.forms and .Net Maui).
- The applications we develop are for Android, IOS and Windows.

Junior Software Developer - Netcompany Intrasoft

FEB 2023 - SEP 2023

- I worked as a Full Stack developer and I coded Java, with Spring framework and primefaces. The project was the medical file and other many services for hospitals.
- Some of the technologies I used was WebLogic Server, Toad Database, SoapUI, Postman, Jenkins and Arifactory.

Associate Software Engineer - Wappier

AUG 2022 - FEB 2023

- I worked as a Backend developer and I coded with Rust. I used the Axum framework from the Tokio library
- Some of the technologies I used with Rust was GraphQl, Kafka, Docker, Redis, MongoDB, PostgresDB, Prometheus, Grafana and Postman
- I have experience programming and developing software with teams implementing Agile methodologies.

Check-In Agent - Goldair Handling

JUL 2021 - SEP 2021

I was Check-In Agent for Aegean Airlines

Languages

- Greek
- English

Hobbies

Gym

Running

Box

Trips